What am I sitting on?
我是坐到什麼東東啊？
Top of the world?
世界頂端？
Dock of the bay?
河堤碼頭？ （歌詞）
I'm out.
想不出來了
Oh,undies!
內褲
Whose are they?
老實說，誰的？
-Whose are they? -Not mine.
誰的？ 不是我的
Joey's! Got to be Joey's.
是喬伊的，一定是他的
They're mine.
的確是我的
See,Joey's. They're Joe-Joe-Joey's.
看吧？就是喬伊的，喬…伊的
Why are they here?
怎麼會在這裡？
I don't know.
我不知道…
Because I'm Joey.
因為我是喬伊
I'm disgusting.
我生性齷齪
I take my underwear off in other people's homes.
隨便在別人家脫內褲
Get them out of here. What's wrong with you?
快拿走，你哪裡有病啊？
對啊 好惡
-Take them! -I got them.
拿去啊
You can touch them. They're yours.
喬伊，你幹嘛不敢碰 這是你的內褲
Chandler? A word?
錢德，借一步說話 好
I'm tired of covering for you two. This has got to stop.
我受夠了 不想再幫你們說謊了 這種鳥事不能再發生了
Tighty-whiteys? What are you,8?
而且還是白色三角褲？ 你8歲嗎？
Thank you,Joey,so much.
謝謝你，喬伊，感激不盡
You're not welcome,okay?
我家不歡迎你
Look,I hate this. You guys keep embarrassing me.
我討厭這樣 你們害我拚命出醜
Yesterday,Rachel found your razor in our bathroom.
昨天瑞秋在這裡的浴室 看到你的剃刀
I said it was mine, and that I was playing a woman in a play.
我只好說是我的 還說我要在話劇裡演女人
Then one thing led to another,and....
結果還得一不做二不休
And around the ankles, that is a tough spot.
連腳踝周圍都剃光了 那裡很不好刮哩
It was. All right,listen
沒錯，告訴你們，我不能…
All this lying has been hard on us too.
我們要說謊也不好受
Yeah,I bet all the sex makes it easier.
是喔，不過至少你們有上床
Yeah,actually.
那倒是
Meanwhile,I get Rachel shoving your underwear in my face...
瑞秋不僅把你的內褲 湊到我面前
...and asking when she can come see me star in Ugly Woman.
還問什麼時候 可以看我演出醜女人
We'll be more careful.
我們下次一定會更小心
We don't want them to know because it's going really well.
因為我們實在太甜蜜了 所以不想告訴別人
And maybe it's going well because it's a secret.
搞不好就是保密才能這麼順利
It sounds weird, but we're so bad at relationships.
我知道你覺得很怪 但我們都不太會處理感情問題
-We are. Help us! -Help!
沒錯，幫幫忙 拜託
All right. But you do it with me once.
好吧，不過…你要跟我上床一次
-Joey! -Didn't think so.
喬伊 就知道你不肯
The One With Ross' Sandwich
本集播出：「真相不白」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
-Can we please just drop this? -But I don't get it.
不能換個話題嗎？ 可是我實在不懂
Does anybody else just take off their underwear when they're hot?
別人一熱也會隨便 在朋友家脫內褲嗎？
菲比
What are you reading?
你在看什麼？
Wuthering Heights.
「咆哮山莊」
I have to finish it by tomorrow for my literature class.
我在紐恩大學上文學課 明天之前必須看完
You're taking a class? That's so cool.
我不知道你在上課，真酷
I really liked that Lamaze class I took.
上次上拉梅茲課很好玩
I thought this time I'd go for something more intellectual...
所以我決定換種課來上 換點比較要用腦袋
...with a less painful final exam.
期末考又不用那麼痛苦的
That sounds like fun.
聽起來很有意思
Oh,you should come with me!
你也可以一起來
Then I'll have someone to sit with.
就有人可以跟我一起坐了
好啊
Do you have time to read it?
不過你有時間看書嗎？
I read it in school.
我高中就念過那本了
This is going to be so much fun! I have to finish.
一定很好玩 噓，先讓我看完
But what time does the class start?
幾點要上課？
嗨
What's wrong,buddy?
你怎麼啦？
Someone at work ate my sandwich.
有同事偷吃我的三明治
What did the police say?
條子怎麼說？
My Thanksgiving leftover sandwich.
那是感恩節剩下的三明治
I can't believe someone ate it.
竟然給人偷吃掉
It's just a sandwich.
不過是個三明治嘛
Just a sandwich?
不過是個三明治？
I am 30 years old,okay?
我今年30歲，
I'll be divorced twice and I got evicted.
已經離婚兩次 還沒地方可住
That sandwich was the only good thing in my life!
那個三明治是我人生中 唯一美好的事情
Someone ate the only good thing going on in my life!
結果唯一美好的事情 竟然給人偷吃掉
That's a nice sweater vest.
這件毛線背心不錯
I have enough for one more sandwich.
我還有材料可以再做一個三明治
I was going to eat it myself,but....
我本來自己要吃…
Mon,that would be incredible. Thank you so much.
太好了，真是謝謝你
I still can't believe someone ate it!
我到現在還不相信有人偷吃了
Look,I left a note and everything.
我還留了一張紙條在上面
"Knock-knock." "Who's there?"
「叩叩叩」，「誰啊？」
"Ross Geller's lunch."
「羅斯蓋勒的午餐」
"Ross Geller's lunch,who?"
「哪個羅斯蓋勒的午餐？」
"Ross Geller's lunch. Please don't take me. Okay?"
「這是羅斯蓋勒的午餐 請勿偷走我」
I'm surprised you didn't wear it home.
你沒被扁就該偷笑了
Want to keep your food? Scare people off.
不想讓別人偷吃你的東西？ 那就得嚇跑他們
I learned that on the street.
這是我在街頭流浪學到的
Really?
真的？
What would you say,Phoebe?
不然你怎麼說，菲比？
Stuff like: "Keep your mitts off my grub."
例如「髒手少碰我的餿水」？
Do you picture Phoebe on the street with the entire cast of Annie?
羅斯，你以為菲比 當年是在演溫苦女流浪記嗎？
This'll keep them away from your stuff.
貼上這張紙條就沒人敢偷吃了
哇
Phoebe,you are a badass!
菲比，你真狠
Someday I'll tell you how I stabbed the cop.
下次再告訴你們 我拿刀捅條子的事
He stabbed me first!
是他先捅我的
The Bronte sisters were remarkable women for their time.
布朗蒂姐妹是當代的傑出女性
They lived in a patriarchal society.
當時是父系社會
Sorry I'm late, but I left late.
抱歉遲到，因為我太晚出門
So,what is the book about?
菲比，這本書在說什麼？
Didn't you read it in high school?
你說你高中念過
I started it,but then there was this pep rally.
對，後來我想起我開始看時 正好碰上要為球隊打氣
And I was on top of the pyramid.
我又是啦啦隊隊長
But anyway...
就是這樣啦…
...what's the book about?
到底在說什麼？
It's a tragic love story between Cathy and Heathcliff.
這是凱西跟希克裡夫的 悲慘愛情故事
It takes place on these creepy moors in England.
故事發生在英國可怕的山莊
Which I think represent the wildness of Heathcliff's character.
場景就代表 男主角性格中狂野的一面
I totally get symbolism.
我對象徵主義很有一套
How would you characterize the theme of this book?
這本書的主題是什麼？
Let's see.... Rachel Greene?
看看找誰…瑞秋葛林
I would have to say that it's a tragic love story.
這是個…愛情悲劇
That's sort of a given...
非常明顯
...but,yes. Anyone else?
不過你說得也沒錯 還有誰有意見？
Symbolism!
還有象徵性的意義
And the wildness of the moors...
狂野的場景…
...which I think,is mirrored...
反映出
...in the wildness of Heathcliff's character.
男主角性格中桀傲的一面
Excellent! What Rachel has shrewdly observed here....
非常好 瑞秋讀得相當透徹
You completely stole my answer!
你根本就是照我說的回答
Honey,that was pretty obvious.
親愛的，隨便讀讀就知道了
How would you know? You didn't read it!
你哪曉得？你根本沒念過
What do you think? You in the blue shirt?
你有何意見呢？ 穿藍襯衫這位同學？
I think that yours is a question with many possible answers.
我認為這個問題 有很多可能的答案
Would you care to venture one?
那就麻煩你舉出一個
你願意說一個嗎？
Are you just repeating me?
你是重複我的話嗎？
All right. Let's move on.
好吧，我們看下去
Okay,then.
好
Why didn't you say you hadn't read the book?
你為什麼不直接說你沒看過？
I didn't want him to think I was stupid.
我不希望他認為我很蠢
That was really embarrassing, what happened to you.
你看看你多糗 菲比 怎麼了？
Your note?
你那張紙條
Amazing!
真是了不起
Not only did no one touch my sandwich...
不但沒人敢碰我的三明治
...but people at work are actually afraid of me.
而且還開始對我敬畏三分
A guy called me "Mental."
還有人叫我瘋子
"Mental Geller."
瘋子蓋勒
I've always wanted a cool nickname like that.
我一直夢想有這種超酷外號
The best you got in high school was "Wet Pants Geller."
以前你最酷的外號 就是「尿褲子蓋勒」
It was the water fountain,okay?!
那是飲水機噴到的
Anyway...
現在...
...people are writing reports for me...
有人願意幫我寫報告
...pushing back deadlines to fit my schedule.
我愛什麼時候交就什麼時候交
I tell you, you get tough with people...
原來對人耍狠...
...and you can get anything you want.
...就可以呼風喚雨
Hey,Tribbiani! Give me that coffee! Now!
崔比亞尼，咖啡拿來
This was really fun.
今天真有意思
I've been wondering if you'd ask me out.
我本來還懷疑你會不會約我
So you still wondering?
你還在懷疑嗎？
No. We just went out.
我們已經去約會啦
You're smart.
你真聰明
I like that.
我喜歡
Oh,candles!
還有蠟燭啊
What is that,a blanket?
這是什麼？毯子？
A video camera? Oh,my God!
攝影機？ 我的天啊
I can't believe you thought you'd tape us having sex on the first date!
你竟然第一次約會 就想拍下我們上床過程
你好
Joey,is what she just said....
喬伊，她剛說的…
Oh,my God!
天啊
You're actually going
你還真打算…
What is going on here?
這是怎麼回事？
And with Chandler in the next room. What are you,sick?
而且錢德還在家 你是…你是變態嗎？
I'm Joey.
我是喬伊啊
I mean, I'm disgusting.
我本來就噁心
I make low-budget adult films.
還拍低成本的A片
You promised to be more careful!
你們答應我要更小心的
The good Joey name's been dragged through the mud!
喬伊的好名聲都給你們毀了
We're so sorry.
對不起 抱歉
I'm telling everyone.
我要把你們的事情說出去
It's the only explanation that doesn't make me look like a pig!
否則內褲跟攝影機的事情 只會讓人覺得我是變態豬玀
No,there's a better explanation.
等一下，一定有其他方法
Tell them you had to make an adult film for your...
你可以說你在拍A片 因為你在…
...adult film class.
...上A片課
I like that. But no!
這理由還不錯 不過不行
How does that explain my underwear at your place?
瑞秋在你家發現我內褲的事又怎麼說？
I don't know.
不知道
Get ready to come out of the non-gay closet.
看來你們得出櫃承認了
I promise to come up with something. Just give us time.
拜託你等等 我保證一定會想出理由 再多給我們緩幾天
All right.
好吧
But it better make me look really good.
最好讓我保住面子
And another thing:
還有…
The video camera?
攝影機？
Nice!
神來之筆！
「史前歷史博物館」
May I have a word?
羅斯，可以跟你談談嗎？
Of course,Donald.
當然，唐諾
We've been getting reports of very angry behavior on your part.
有同事抱怨你最近脾氣火爆
-What? -Threatening letters...
什麼？ 寫信威脅大家...
...refusal to meet deadlines.
拒絕按時交報告
Apparently people now call you Mental.
還有人說你是瘋子
是啊
We want you to speak to a psychiatrist.
我們希望你找精神科醫生談談
You don't understand. This is so silly.
不，你不懂，其實是誤會
This is all just because of a sandwich.
一切要從我的三明治說起
A sandwich?
三明治？
You see,my sister makes these amazing turkey sandwiches.
我妹妹非常會做火雞三明治
Her secret is,she puts an extra slice of gravy-soaked bread in the middle.
她的秘訣就是 多夾一片浸過肉汁的麵包
I call it "The Moistmaker."
我稱那片為「多汁秘方」
Anyway,I put my sandwich in the fridge....
有一次我把三明治放在冰箱
Oh,you know what?
你知道嗎？ 什麼？
I'm sorry.
對不起
I believe I ate that.
應該是我吃掉了
You ate my sandwich?
你吃了我的三明治？
A simple mistake. It can happen to anyone.
我一時看錯，誰都可能拿錯
Oh,really?
是嗎？
Did you confuse it with your own turkey sandwich with a Moistmaker?
難道你的三明治 也有「多汁秘方」？
Do you,perhaps,remember...
難道...
...seeing a note on top of it?
...你沒看到上面的紙條？
There may have been a joke or limerick of some kind.
我以為那是有人開玩笑 或是隨手寫的打油詩
That said it was...
上面清楚地寫著...
...my sandwich!
...那是我的三明治
Now,calm down.
你別激動
Look in my office. Some may be in the trash.
可以到我辦公室找找 可能垃圾筒裡還有剩
What？
什麼？
It was quite large. I had to throw most of it away.
那個三明治很大 我哪裡吃得了那麼多
You threw my sandwich away?
你…丟掉我的三明治
My sandwich?!
我的三明治
What's this book about?
這本書在講什麼？
You didn't read it,either?
你這本也沒看？
I was going to,but I accidentally read something else.
我本來要看，結果看了別本書
Vogue.
「時尚雜誌」
So tell me about Jane Eyre.
這個簡愛是幹嘛的？
No,read it yourself.
不行，你應該自己看
Come on, don't be such a goody-goody.
菲比，別這麼假正經嘛
Fine.
好吧
All right. So,Jane Eyre?
簡愛呢…
First,you'd think she's a woman, but she's not.
你會以為她是女人 其實不然
She's a cyborg.
她是生化人
A cyborg? Isn't that like a robot?
生化人？就是機器人？
This book was light years ahead of its time.
這本書在當時超級先進
Sorry I'm late. Let's get started.
抱歉遲到，開始上課吧
What did you think of Jane Eyre?
大家對簡愛有何感想？
Rachel and I were discussing it, and she had very interesting insights.
瑞秋剛跟我討論過 她有些看法非常有趣
Go ahead,Rachel.
請說，瑞秋
Thank you,Phoebe.
謝謝你，菲比
What struck me most when reading Jane Eyre...
簡愛最讓我震驚的就是
...was how the book was so ahead of its time.
這本書非常驚世駭俗
If you're talking about feminism, I think you're right.
如果你指的是女性主義 這麼說也成
Well,feminism,yes. But also the robots.
當然有寫到女性主義 不過還有機器人
嘿 嘿
Since that video camera thing didn't work out...
既然上次要拍攝不成功
...I thought that I would give you just a little preview.
我先給你一點預告片段
You're naked!
你沒穿衣服
I know!
我知道
羅斯
錢德
摩妮卡
Are you okay?
羅斯，你沒事吧？
I'm fine.
我很好
I saw a psychiatrist at work today.
我今天上班去看過精神醫生
Why?
為什麼？
On account of my rage.
因為我脾氣太暴躁
Which,if I may say, right now is out of control.
而且最近越來越嚴重
He gave me a pill for it.
所以他開藥丸給我
A pill?
藥丸？
When the psychiatrist told me to take a leave of absence...
醫生說我應該請假
...because I yelled at my boss, I started to get worked up again.
因為我對上司大吼大叫 我又開始暴跳如雷
So he offered me a tranquilizer.
所以他要我吃顆鎮定劑
And I thought it was a good idea.
我覺得這主意不錯
So I took it.
所以就吃了
They're making you take time off work?
等等，他們逼你請假？
And you're okay with that?
而且你也同意？
I don't know.
我不曉得
It's going to be weird not having a job for a while.
剛開始不工作可能不習慣
But I definitely don't care about my sandwich.
不過我已經不在乎三明治了
I hate it when they make me see the shrink at my office.
公司逼我看心理醫生時 我也很火大
He's always like, "Your colleagues will like you better if you like yourself better."
他老說「如果你多愛自己 同事就會更喜歡你」
Who needs that?
誰需要這套垃圾？
-You do. -I know.
你啊 我知道
It's so embarrassing! I can't believe you let me go on like that!
我丟臉丟大了 你竟然還讓我說下去
I'm sorry.
對不起
It was so funny when you compared Jane Eyre to Robocop.
你把簡愛比做機器戰警 實在太爆笑了
That was not funny!
一點也不好笑
I snapped,okay? You weren't taking the class seriously.
我太氣了 你根本不想好好上課
Come on! What is the big deal?
菲比，這有什麼了不起？
I thought it'd be something we could do together.
我以為我們就是一起出去
I thought it would be fun.
上課打發時間鬧著玩
Fun is good.
好玩很重要
But I also wanted to learn.
但是我也想學點東西
People talk about what they learned in high school. I never went.
大家老說在高中學東學西 我卻沒上過高中
So you really wanted to learn.
所以你真心想上課
You know,Phoebe, I just wanted to have fun.
但是我只想找點樂子
You know who should go?
你知道你該拉誰去嗎？
I know! I know! I know!
我知道…
Monica,you asked the question.
摩妮卡，問題是你提的
Oh,my God,that's Monica!
天啊，是摩妮卡
No，no，no
You get away from me, you sick,sick,sicko!
離我遠點，你這個大變態
What's going on?
怎麼啦？
Joey has got a secret peephole!
喬伊偷看大家
-Oh,no! -Yes,he has a naked picture of Monica!
天啊… 他有摩妮卡的裸體照片
He takes naked pictures of us,then he eats chicken and looks at them!
他拍下我們裸體的樣子 還一邊吃雞塊一邊看
Oh! Dude,that's my sister!
你們看 那是我老妹耶
Give me that!
給我
Wait! Everybody calm down,okay?
等一下，大家先別激動
Let's give our friend a chance to explain why he's such a big pervert!
要給我們的老友喬伊 有機會解釋他為何如此病態
I am not a pervert,okay?
我不是變態好嗎？
It's just....
只是…
I just kind of....
我…其實…
I think I can explain this.
大家聽我說，我可以幫他解釋
Thank you.
謝謝
Joey's a sex addict.
喬伊是性愛狂
What?! No,I'm not!
什麼？才怪
It's okay! It's good!
沒關係，不怪你
It's a disease.
這只是一種病
I am not a sex addict!
胡說，我才不是性愛狂
Yes,you are!
你明明就是
That's the only way to explain all this stuff!
這才能解釋最近這一連串的事
No,it isn't. It's not.
事實不是這樣
Because you could also explain it with the truth!
你也可以說出真相
What is the truth?
什麼真相？
-What's up? -What's going on?
怎麼回事？ 你在說什麼？
I slept with Monica.
我跟摩妮卡上床了
Well, let's see what everybody thinks of that.
聽聽大家怎麼說？
天啊
You slept with my sister?
你跟我老妹上床？
Yes,but it was
對 不過...
We just did it once,in London.
只在倫敦發生過一次
This is not good for my rage.
這會讓我開始抓狂
Is this true?
摩妮卡，是真的嗎？
Of course,it's true.
當然是真的
How else would you explain all the weird stuff that's been going on?
否則怎麼解釋這些怪事？
Yes,it's true.
是真的
If it happened once,how come we found your underwear in our apartment?
如果只發生過一次 你的內褲 怎麼會出現在我們家？
That was the underwear I was wearing that night in London.
那件內褲是我當天在倫敦穿的
Right,Monica?
對不對，摩妮卡？
I guess I wanted to keep it...
我想留下來…
...as a souvenir.
...當紀念品
My God,Monica!
天啊，摩妮卡
Are you sure you're not just a sex addict?
你確定，喬伊？ 你確定你不是性愛狂？
If anyone's a sex addict here, it's Monica.
要是有人是性愛狂 那也是摩妮卡
She has been trying to get me back in the sack ever since London!
沒錯，打從我們自倫敦回來 她就想再勾引我上床
That's why she gave you a naked picture of herself.
所以她才拍裸照給你
That makes sense.
這樣說得通
And the video camera?
錄影機呢？
摩妮卡？
I guess I set up the video camera to try and entice Joey.
我架好錄影機是為了 引誘喬伊上鉤
But,sadly, I could not be enticed.
可惜我不吃這套
Monica,this has to stop now.
摩妮卡，你不能再這樣下去
I know,I know.
我知道…
I know. I will,and I would appreciate if we all could just...
我知道 我會的 希望大家立刻忘了這件事
...drop it immediately,and forever.
以後再也別提起
Okay. That is,if you can resist me.
只要你能抵抗我的魅力
-I'll give it my best shot. -Good luck.
我會盡量努力 祝你好運了
Unbelievable!
不可思議
You really kept Joey's underwear?
你還留下喬伊的內褲？
Why? Why would you do that?
為什麼？你為什麼這麼做？
I'm Monica.
因為我是摩妮卡
I'm disgusting.
生性下流
I stalk guys and keep their underpants.
我會跟蹤男人 留下他們的內褲
I think we've all learned who's disgusting and who's not.
現在終於知道誰是噁心鬼了
Now,I'm going to get back to my bucket.
好了，我要開始吃炸雞了
I'm only eating the skin, so the chicken's up for grabs.
我只吃雞皮，你們可以吃雞肉
You were making a good point.
你說得很有道理
I mean,till you got cut off.
可惜後來被打斷
What's up with that girl Monica?
那個摩妮卡哪裡有病啊？
I don't know. I didn't come with her.
誰曉得？她不是我朋友
Hey,everybody! Everybody,guess what!
好消息，各位 你們猜怎麼了？
I just convinced Carl to give us a test.
我說服保羅下周考試
Test?
考試？
Come on! Tests make us all better learners!
開心點，有考試才有進步
Oh,yeah! We should have essay questions!
對了，應該考申論題